My boy.
我的儿子
My little Hercules.
我的小海克力斯
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh~~
啊
ugh
呃啊
Hold on, kiddo! What's your hurry?
等等孩子 你着什么急
After all these years...is this the kind of hello you give your father?
这么多年没见面 你就是这么给你的老父亲打招呼的吗
F-Father?
父 父亲
Didn't know you had a famous father, did you?
没想到你的亲生父亲这么有名气吧
Surprise!
惊不惊喜 意不意外
Look how you've grown.
看看 你都长这么大了
Why, you've got your mother's beautiful eyes...
看看 你继承了你母亲漂亮的眼睛
and my strong chin.
还有我坚毅的下巴
Hah!
哈
I-I don't understand.
我 我不明白
If you're my father,
如果你是我父亲
that would make me a...
那么我就是
A god.
一位天神
A god!
Hey, you wanted answers,
你想知道答案
and by thunder...you're old enough now to know the truth.
我的孩子你已经长大成人可以知道真相了
But why did you leave me on Earth?
你们为什么把我丢在凡间呢
Didn't you want me?
难道是因为不想要我吗
Of course we did.
我们怎么可能不要你
Your mother and I loved you with all our hearts.
你母亲和我对你视若珍宝
But someone stole you from us and turned you mortal...
但是有人把你从我们身边偷走并且将你变成凡人
and only gods can live on Mount Olympus.
而只有神明之躯才能住在奥林匹斯山上
And you can't do a thing?
而且你无能为力是吗
I can't, Hercules, but you can.
我解决不了 但是你可以啊 海克力斯
R-Really? W-What? I'll do anything.
真 真的吗 要怎么做 我什么都愿意
Hercules, if you can prove yourself a true hero on Earth...
海克力斯 如果你能在人间证明自己是一位真正的英雄
your godhood will be restored.
你的神格就能得以恢复
A true hero. Great!
真正的英雄 太棒了